MARSHALL LANNERS SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Summary

Full stack web developer and software engineer with 6+ years of customer service, and 2 years office management experience. Excellent team player, reliable, trustworthy, and curious individual always seeking ways to learn new technologies. Solid understanding of HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node, Python, and C.

Projects

Tryspaw.com

July 2019 to Oct. 2019

Software engineer consultant specializing in frontend technologies React, Javascript, HTML and CSS. Works individually and in a team format to meet sprint deadlines in an agile work environment.

Let's Get Tacos

HTML | React | Node | Redux | CSS | Firebase | Heroku

Developed on a team of 4, built in 5 weeks, integrated Api, contributed to React, Node backend, and UI for application.

Application interacts with the Yelp and Google Maps Api to schedule events for users to meetup and eat tacos together.

Github: https://github.com/Lambda-School-Labs/labs10-taco-run

Website: https://taco-run-c453f.firebaseapp.com/

Spotty

HTML | React | CSS | Firebase | Heroku Individual project

Application uses the Spotify Api for users to interact listen to music and post music tracks to their Spotify account.

Github: https://github.com/lanners-marshall/spotty Website: https://react-spotty.herokuapp.com/

Employment

Lambda School

Remote

Seattle

Lambda School Team/Support Hour Lead

July 2019 to Current

Mentors students in full stack web development along with handling student attendance and progress, conducting standup meetings, grading assignments, and teaching course material.

Ricoh @ Amazon

Senior on Site

July 2016 to Nov. 2018

Operated high volume business to meet all their shipping needs of Amazon employees, utilized high volume duplicating equipment, performed associated copying tasks, provided copier maintenance and repair of customer site equipment.

Contact

- lanners.marshall@gmail.com
- mlanners.com
- **206-475-7021**
- **♥** Seattle, Wa
- in mlanners/
- (C) lanners-marshall

Skills

HTML CSS

REACT

NODE

JAVASCRIPT PYTHON

Education

Lambda School Sept. 2018 to Mar. 2019

Certificate Full Stack Web
Development and Computer
Science

California Polytechnic University

May 2007 to Jan. 2010

Bachelor of Science Business Administration, Management